how do we ready yes for round one
كيف نجهز نعم لجولة واحدة
category five technology TV the game
الفئة الخامسة تكنولوجيا التلفزيون اللعبة
show now on July 17th my birthday
تظهر الآن في 17 يوليو عيد ميلادي
yes 2012 you and I were sitting on the
نعم كنت أنا و 2012 كنت جالسا على
set we did an amazing show in Studio C
وضعنا عرضًا رائعًا في Studio C
it was a fun show but here we are more
كان عرض مرح ولكن هنا نحن أكثر
than five years later and unfortunately
بعد خمس سنوات ولسوء الحظ
the files are corrupted so all we have
الملفات تالفة لذا كل ما لدينا
now is the video and the audio is
الآن هو الفيديو والصوت هو
completely kaput so fortunately the
تماما kaput لذلك لحسن الحظ
video is there and fortunately we have a
الفيديو هناك ولحسن الحظ لدينا
resident professional lip reader you do
قارءات الشفة المهنية المقيمة لديك
sign language that's all I can do and
لغة الإشارة كل ما يمكنني القيام به و
you've been doing this all your life so
كنت قد تم القيام بذلك طوال حياتك حتى
what better person to help me to recover
ما أفضل شخص لمساعدتي في الشفاء
this show so what we're going to do
هذا العرض حتى ما نحن بصدد القيام به
tonight is we're going to use your
الليلة نحن ذاهبون لاستخدام الخاص بك
capabilities to flawlessly read the lips
قدرات لقراءة الشفاه بسهولة
from episode number what did I say it
من رقم الحلقة ماذا قلت
was 252 and let's see if we can piece
كان 252 ودعونا نرى ما اذا كنا نستطيع
this back together and bring this
هذا مرة أخرى معا وجلب هذا
episode back from 2012
حلقة من عام 2012
[Music]
[موسيقى]
what's going on with Wayne weird it's
ما يجري مع وين غريب
true I'm a princess nope Tai Chi is my
صحيح أنا أميرة كلا تاي تشي هو بلدي
Fang people are the worst some people
فانغ الناس هم أسوأ بعض الناس
are Buddhists to Buddha's and if that
بوذيون إلى بوذا وإذا كان ذلك
day of the month then the day of the
يوم من الشهر ثم يوم
poopoo is a Thursday when eerie the boa
poopoo هو يوم الخميس عندما غريب الأفعى
and finally I got you what I knew you
وأخيراً حصلت على ما أعرفك
would always want I knew you wanted this
كنت أريد دائما أن أعرف أنك تريد هذا
it's a birthday girl matches your dress
انها فتاة عيد ميلاد مباريات اللباس الخاص بك
perfectly I know and you figured I know
تماما وأنا أعلم وكنت أحسب أنني أعلم
I'd want to try - birthday boy
كنت أريد أن أحاول - فتى عيد ميلاد
[Music]
[موسيقى]
hmm that's terrific babies cry and I
هم هذا صرخات رائع يبكي وأنا
hope I don't get wet tonight once we get
آمل ألا أكون رطبة الليلة عندما نحصل
the shrapnel off this toad Oh God
الشظايا من هذا الضفدع يا الله
now of course I have to call Finn from
الآن بالطبع لا بد لي من استدعاء فين من
Star Wars to get the lightsabers same
حرب النجوم للحصول على نفس الأضواء
their sports I need more light I think I
رياضتهم أنا بحاجة إلى مزيد من الضوء وأعتقد أنني
should go back to the future
يجب أن نعود إلى المستقبل
why Wow hurts your DeLorean part I'll
لماذا يؤلمك نجاح باهر في ديللوريان
just be quick and your back for John
فقط كن سريعًا وظهرك لجون
before juice it's going to be a movie a
قبل العصير سيكون فيلم
Jamba Juice movie it's gonna be me if
Jamba Juice movie it's gonna be me if
you think I'm gonna cry I don't have any
كنت أعتقد أنني سأبكي ليس لدي أي
property and like sugar
الممتلكات ومثل السكر
I prayed something Bad's gonna happen
صليت ستعمل شيء سيء ليحدث
and I'm back from the future who are you
وأنا عدت من المستقبل من أنت
Freddie Mercury
فريدي ميركوري
[Music]
[موسيقى]
unfair oh and you lose them wasting the
غير عادل يا وتفقدهم إهدار
paper pickles mumbo-jumbo we do we do
مخللات الورق mumbo-jumbo نقوم به
way oh my goodness hi guys it's so well
طريقة يا الهي يا رفاق انها على ما يرام
Hilary ten points for Hillary in round
هيلاري عشر نقاط لهيلاري في الدور
one Oh paper tickles oh boy
واحد يا ورقة دغدغة يا صبي
[Music]
[موسيقى]
[Applause]
[تصفيق]